Guide to the Farm Bureau scrapbooks, New York State,1912-1934.
Farm Bureau scrapbooks, New York State,1912-1934.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Farm Bureau scrapbooks, New York State, 1912-1934.
21-24-472
4.2 cubic ft.
Receipts, bulletins, photographs.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Scrapbooks documenting farm bureau activities county by county, 1912-1917; also two scrapbooks on farm bureau activity statewide, 1928-1934.
Between 1911 and 1918, Farm Bureaus were organized by Cornell's College of Agriculture in most rural counties in New York State, before 1914 with the assistance of Sears Roebuck, railroads, chambers of commerce, and other business groups, after 1914 with federal aid provided under the Smith-Lever Act. In 1918, these bureaus and those which had been organized simultaneously in other states organized nationally as the American Farm Bureau Federation. Within New York, the county farm bureaus were organized as the New York State Farm Bureau Federation. The integration of Cooeperative Extension and the Farm Bureaus continued in New York State into the 1950s, when separation was mandated by the federal government.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Scrapbooks documenting farm bureau activities county by county, 1912-1917; also two scrapbooks on farm bureau activity statewide, 1928-1934.
SUBJECTS
Names:
American Farm Bureau Federation.; New York State Farm Bureau Federation.
Subjects:
Agriculture--Societies, etc.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. 1916-1917
Series II. 1918
Series III. 1919
Series IV.1920
Series V. 1921
Series VI. 1922
Series VII. 1923
Series VIII. 1924
Series IX. 1925
Series X. 1926
Series XI. 1927
Series XII. 1928
Series XIII. 1929
Series XIV. 1930
Series XV. 1931
Series XVI. 1932
Series XVII. 1933
Series XVIII.1934
Series XIX. 1935
Series XX. 1936
Series XXI. 1937
Series XXII. 1938
Series XXIII. 1939
Series XXIV. Constitutions and Bylaws
Series XXV. Memorandums
Series XXVI. Committee Meetings
Series XXVII. Correspondence
Series XXVIII. Flood and Drought Relief
Series XXIX. Land Use Project
Series XXX. Extension Files
Series XXXI. Soil Conservation Districts
Series XXXII. 1952
Series XXXIII. 1953
Series XXXIV. 1954
Series XXXV. 1955
Series XXXVI. Farm and Home Bureau and 4-H Club Association
Series XXXVII. 1956
Series XXXVIII. Miscellaneous
Series XXXIX. Farm Management Office
Series XL. Photographs
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. 1916-1917
  - Albany County, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Allegany County, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Broome County, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cattaraugua County, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cayuga County, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Chautauqua County, 1916-1917 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Chemung County, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Chenango County, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Clinton County, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Clinton County, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Cortland County, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Delaware County, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Dutchess County, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Erie County, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Essex County, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Greene County, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Herkimer County, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Jefferson County, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Jefferson County, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Madison County, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Monroe County, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Monroe County, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Montgomery County, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Nassau County - Photos, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Nassau County, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Onondaga County, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Orange County, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Orleans County, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Oswego County, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Otsego County, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Rennselaer County, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Rockland County, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Saratoga County, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Schoharie County, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Suffolk County, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Sullivan and Ulster County, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Sullivan County, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Tioga County, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Tompkins County, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Ulster County, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Warren County, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Wayne County, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Westchester County, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Westchester County, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Series II. 1918
  - Albany County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Allegany County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Broome County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Cattaraugua County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Cayuga County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Chatauqua County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Chemung County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Chenago County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Clinton County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Columbia County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Cortland County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Delaware County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Dutchess County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Erie County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Essex County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Fulton County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Genesee County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Greene County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Herkimer County, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Jefferson County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Lewis County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Livingston County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Madison County, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Monroe County, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Montogmery County, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Nassau County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Niagara County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Oneida County, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Onondaga County, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Orleans County, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Oswego County, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Rensselaer County, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Rockland County, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Saratoga County, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Schenectady County, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Schoharie County, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Schuyler County, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Seneca County, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Steuben County, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Suffolk County, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Tioga County, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Tompkins County, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Ulster County, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Warren County, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Washington County, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Wayne County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Westchester County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Wyoming County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Yates County, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Series III. 1919
  - Albany County, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Allegany County, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Broome County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Cattaraugua County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Cayuga County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Chautauqua County, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Chemung County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Chenango County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Clinton County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Columbia County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Cortland County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Delaware County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Dutchess County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Erie County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Essex County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Franklin County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Fulton County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Genesee County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Greene County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Herkimer County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Jefferson County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Lewis County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Livingston County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Madison County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Monroe County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Montgomery County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Nassau County, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Nester County, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Niagara County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Niagara County, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Oneida County, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Oneida County, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Onondaga County, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Ontario County, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Ontario County, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Orange County, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Orange County, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Orleans County, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Oswego County, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Otsego County, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Otsego County, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Rensselaer County, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Rockland County, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Saratoga County, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Schenectady County, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Schoharie County, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Schuyler County, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Seneca County, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Steuben County, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Suffolk County, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Sullivan County, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Tioga County, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Tompkins County, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Warren County, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Washington County, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Wayne County, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Winchester County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Wyoming County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Yates County, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Series IV. 1920
  - Albany County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Allegany County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Broome County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Cattaraugus County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Cayuga County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Chatauqua County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Chemung County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Chenango County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Clinton County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Columbia County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Cortland County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Delaware County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Dutchess County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Erie County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Essex County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Franklin County, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Fulton County, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Genesee County, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Greene County, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Herkimer County, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Jefferson County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Lewis County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Madison County, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Monroe County, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Montgomery County, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Nassau County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Niagara County, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Oneida County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Onondaga County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Ontario County, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Orange County, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Orleans County, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Oswego County, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Rensselaer County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Rockland County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Saratoga County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Schenectady County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Schoharie County, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Schuyler County, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Seneca County, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Steuben County, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Suffolk County, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Sullivan County, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Tioga County, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Tompkins County, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Ulster County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Warren County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Washington County, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Wayne County, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Wyoming County, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Yates County, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Series V. 1921
  - Albany County, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Allegany County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Broome County, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Cattaraugus County, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Chautauqua County, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Chemung County, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Chenango County, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Clinton County, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Columbia County, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Cortland County, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Delaware County, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Dutchess County, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Erie County, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Essex County, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Franklin County, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Fulton County, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Genesse County, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Greene County, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Herkimer County, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Jefferson County, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Lewis County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Livingston County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Madison County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Monroe County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Montgomery County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Nassau County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Niagra County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Oneida County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Onondaga County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Ontario County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Orange County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Orleans County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Oswego County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Otsego County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Rensselaer County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Rockland County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Saratoga County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Schenectady County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Schoharie County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Schuyler County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Seneca County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Steuben County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Suffolk County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Sullivan County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Tioga County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Tompkins County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Ulster County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Ulster-Sullivan County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Warren County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Washington County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Wayne County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Westchester County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Wyoming County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Yates County, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Series VI. 1922
  - Albany County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Allegany County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Broome County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Cattaraugus County, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Cayuga County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Chautaugua County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Chemung County, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Chenango County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Clinton County, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Columbia County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Cortland County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Delaware County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Delaware County, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Dutchness County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Erie County, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Essex County, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Franklin County, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Fulton County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Genesee County, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Greene County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Herkimer County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Jefferson County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Lewis County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Livingston County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Madison County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Monroe County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Montgomery County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Nassau County, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Niagra County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Oneida County, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Onondaga County, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Ontario County, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Orange County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Orleans County, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Oswego County, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Otsego County, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Rensselaer County, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Saratoga County, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Schenectady County, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Schoharie County, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Schuyler County, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Seneca County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Steuben County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Suffolk County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Sullivan County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Tioga County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Tompkins County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Ulster County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Warren County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Washington County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Wayne County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Westchester County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Wyoming County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Yates County, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Series VII. 1923
  - Albany County, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Allegany County, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Broome County, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Cattaraugus County, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Cayuga County, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Chautauqua County, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Chemung County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Chenango County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Clinton County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Columbia County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Cortland County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Delaware County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Dutchess County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Erie County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Essex County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Franklin County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Fulton County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Genesee County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Greene County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Herkimer County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Jefferson County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Lewis County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Livingston County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Madison County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Monroe County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Montgomery County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Nassau County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Niagara County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Oneida County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Onondaga County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Ontario County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Orange County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Orleans County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Oswego County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Otsego County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Rensselaer County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Rockland County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Saratoga County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Schenectady County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Schoharie County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Schuyler County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Seneca County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Steuben County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Suffolk County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Sullivan County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Tioga County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Tompkins County, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Ulster County, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Warren County, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Washington County, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Wayne County, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Westchester County, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Wyoming County, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Yates County, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Series VIII. 1924, 1924
  - Albany County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Allegany County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Broome County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Cattaraugus County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Cayuga County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Chautaugua County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Chenango County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Clinton County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Cortland County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Dutchess County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Erie County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Erie County, 1924 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Franklin County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Fulton County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Genesee County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Greene County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Herkimer County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Jefferson County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Lewis County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Livingston County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Counties, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Nassau County (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Onandaga County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Ontario County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Otsego County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Saratoga County, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Schenectady County, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Schenectady County, 1924-1925 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Schoharie County, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Schuyler County, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Seneca County, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1924 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Steuben County, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Suffolk County, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Sullivan County, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Sullivan County, 1924-1925 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Tioga County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Tompkins County, 1924 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Ulster County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Ulster-Sullivan County, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Ulster-Sullivan County, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Warren County, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Washington County, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Wayne County, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Westchester County, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Wyoming County, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Yates County, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Series IX. 1925
  - Agricultural County, 1925 and 1927 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Albany County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Allegany County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Broome County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Cattaraugus County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Cattaraugus County, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Cayuga County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Chautaugua County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Chemung County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Chenango County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Clinton County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Columbia County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Cortland County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Delaware County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Dutchess County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Essex County, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Franklin County, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Fulton County, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Genesee County, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Greene County, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Herkimer County, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Herkimer County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Jefferson County, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Jefferson County, 1925, 1926 and 1929 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Lewis County, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Livingston County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Livingston County, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Madison County, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Madison County, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Monroe County, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Montgomery County, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Nassau County, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Niagara County, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Oneida County, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Onondaga County, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Ontario County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Orange County, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Orange County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Orleans County, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Orleans County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Oswego County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Rensselaer County, 1925 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Saratoga County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Schenectady County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Schoharie County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Schuyler County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Seneca County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Steuben County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Steuben County, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Suffolk County, 1925 (Box 34, Folder 1)